What's with these guys?
Are they telling us not to go any farther?
It seems like they're all guarding the ruins.
They might think we’re grave robbers or something.
Look, we're not like that.
Please just let us through.
Like I said, we're not grave robbers.
Hey...!
Wait, brother. Something feels off.
Huh?
Oh...
Brother, these people...
Yeah, this feels like the same pattern as before.
Golems?
Damn it! What is this?
Let's pull back for now!
Why are there golems inside the town?!
Don't ask me, I don't know!
Hey, this is serious! There are monsters called golems over there!
You all need to evacuate right now...
So, the Siam-Sid was a city of golems?!
This is a ruined city! I thought something was strange!
So that's what it was after all!
If you knew that, you could've said so from the start, old man!